# **BROADY G. BUTLER**

2406 Iowa Dr Melbourne, FL 32935 | <u>broadybmx@gmail.com</u> | 618-201-6079

### **SUMMARY**

Project manager with 5 years of experience inspecting concrete restoration projections for condominiums in a corrosive environment. Expertise in interpreting specifications, inspecting construction process, analyzing budgets, and collaborating with multiple teams to meet specific goals. Acquired programming skills through self-taught practice.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

• El License - 2023

#### **CERTIFICATES**

- Freecodecamp.org
  - Legacy Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures
  - Legacy Relational Database

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

• Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Bash

Databases: PostgreSQL

• Version Control Systems: Git

#### **EDUCATION**

**Southern Illinois University Carbondale** - Carbondale, IL **Bachelor of Science: Civil and Environmental Engineering** 

GPA: 3.38

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Keystone Engineering and Consulting -** Cocoa Beach, FL *Project Manager* 

September 2019 – Present

- Documented weekly reports, repair as-built drawings, and photos for multiple projects.
- Monitored construction process and conformance to specifications.
- Verified quality of structural repairs to concrete structures.
- Reported regularly to senior engineers on project budget, progress, and technical problems.
- Maintained open communication by presenting regular updates on project status to customers.
- Facilitated meetings between clients and contractors to discuss deliverables, schedules, and conflicts.

**Illinois Department of Transportation -** Carbondale, IL **Seasonal Engineer Technician Intern**  May 2018 – August 2018 May 2019 – August 2019

- Performed as an assistant to resident engineers.
- Interpreted engineering details for concrete structures and road projects.
- Reviewed technical standards and relevant specifications.
- Calculated quantities to confirm accuracy of the bill of materials.

References available upon request